Dad?
孩子：爸爸
Huh, you know, this place turned out pretty well.
爸爸：你知道吗    这个地方其实很漂亮啊
Almost ashamed to leave, isn't it?
爸爸：离开太可惜了 不是吗
What are you talking...
孩子：你在说什么
I mean...we could stay here if you like.
爸爸：你喜欢的话我们可以待在这
Maybe this time you could even make...
爸爸：或许这次你可以交到
Dad...We didn't get on the ark, did we?
孩子：爸爸   我们不能上船   是不是
I'm sorry, Finny, we're not on the list.
爸爸：对不起   芬尼   我们不在名单上
Ah, I knew they'd turn us away. Nestrians!
孩子：我就知道他们要丢下我们   象鼻兽
We just don't fit in?
孩子：我们就是没法融入
Don't say that! I'll find us a home,
爸爸：不要这样说   我会找到一个家
a place where you'll make friends.
爸爸：一个可以让你交朋友的家
Finny, look at me.
爸爸：芬尼   看着我
I'll get us on the ark ,okay?
爸爸：我会想办法上船的   好吗
You mean it?
孩子：你保证
I give you my word.
爸爸：我保证